<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Group2MOADAssignment</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="blantyre_description">
Blantyre, named after the birth place of the Scottish missionary and explorer, Dr David Livingstone, is the commercial hub of Malawi. Founded in 1876 through the missionary work of the Church of Scotland. It is one of the oldest urban centres in East, Central and Southern Africa and prides itself as having the longest historic and cultural heritage in the region. The tarmac road between Blantyre and Zomba was the first in British Central Africa. The city is Malawi’s centre of commerce and industry and is accessible by road, rail and air links to all parts of Malawi. Must see and do Mandala House St Michaels and All Angels Church Chichiri Museum Art Galleries Curio Markets Markets Michiru Nature Sanctuary Birding Nature Walks Festivals Nightlife, Casinos and entertainment centres Golfing and other sporting activities.

© 2020 - Malawi Department of Tourism
    </string>
    <string name="lilongwe_description">
The Capital City of Malawi and one of the major entry points into the country. It is the seat of government and is located in the central region. Lilongwe started as a small village on the banks of the Lilongwe River, and became a British colonial administrative centre at the start of the 20th century. Lilongwe is sometimes referred to as the green city because of its well tendered gardens and abundant trees, exotic and indigenous.

The City Centre and Capital Hill, where banks, Diplomatic missions and Government ministries are located, are worth visiting. "In the centre of the city, near the referral Kamuzu Central Hospital, is the Lilongwe Nature Sanctuary and Wildlife Centre, an area covering 120 hectares established to give visitors an idea of what the place looked like before construction of the city began. The sanctuary has some animals." "In the centre of the city, near the referral Kamuzu Central Hospital, is the Lilongwe Nature Sanctuary and Wildlife Centre, an area covering 120 hectares established to give visitors an idea of what the place looked like before construction of the city began. The sanctuary has some animals." The city has seen unprecedented development since it assumed capital status. Buildings of modern architectural design are mushrooming everywhere, complimented by the city\'s breathtaking landscape. Lilongwe as a tourist destination has been greatly enhanced, thanks to three multi-million dollar landmark projects under which an International Conference Centre, and the country's first five-star hotel and a modern 40, 000-seat stadium have been built. With the expansion of most of the city's roads into dual carriageways to improve the flow of traffic and ease congestion, a visitor to Lilongwe no longer finds it difficult to travel within the city as was the case in the past. The capital is served by the Kamuzu International Airport, located about 25 Km north of the city. The airport, offers regional and international flight connections.  Malawian Airlines is the national flag carrier. The airport is also serviced by South African Airways, Kenya Airways and Ethiopian Airlines, among others. Must See and Do in Lilongwe Lilongwe Nature Sanctuary Lilongwe Wildlife Centre Botanical gardens War Memorial Park and Kamuzu Mausoleum Kumbali Cultural Village and Permaculture Centre Mbona Shrine Nightlife, Casinos and Entertainment Joints Dzalanyama Forest and Malingunde dam Agri-tourism and village tours.

© 2020 - Malawi Department of Tourism
    </string>
    <string name="mzuzu_description">
Travelling about 367 Km north of Lilongwe, you come to the quiet and beautiful city of Mzuzu, the biggest town in the northern region. It is the country’s third largest city and known for its cool climate. The popular Mzuzu coffee is processed is here. The tea grown here is recognized around the world as being among the world’s finest. To the south of Mzuzu City is Viphya Forest, one of the largest man-made forest in Africa, also containing the third largest rain forest in the world. Like other urban centres, the city has adequate accommodation for tourists visiting the region. Must see and do: Nature walks Nature Sanctuary Bird watching Golfing Mzuzu Museum Historical sites.

© 2020 - Malawi Department of Tourism
    </string>
    <string name="zomba_description">
Located 72km north of Blantyre on a modern road, and 290 Km south of Lilongwe, Zomba is Malawi’s newest city.

It is perched at the foot of the magnificent Zomba Plateau, hence the cool climate. The plateau is    criss-crossed by streams, falls and still dams that cascade through the city.

Zomba was the capital of the British colonial administration and independent Malawi up to 1975 when it was moved to Lilongwe.

The colonial masters may have left many years ago, but their style of architecture is still evident in the city most notably Hotel Masongola; the old Governor’s Residence, old Parliament Building currently serving as the High Court, Gymkhana Club, among others.

Must see and do:

- Kings African Rifles War Memorial Tower
- Hiking
- Nature walks
- Birding
- Trout fishing
- Golfing
- Mountain biking
- Botanical tours
- Horse riding
- Entertainment and Night life
- Village tours
- Market tours
- Berry picking

"Zomba - Islands In The Sky"

© 2020 - Malawi Department of Tourism
    </string>
</resources>